tcdisrupt.com 2014-06-30

# AOL Privacy

This notice provides highlights of the full privacy policy and covers the collection and use of information from any device used to access or connect to AOL branded websites, services, and software, as well as many websites owned by or affiliated with AOL and operating under different names. Para leer este documento en español haz clic [aquí](http://privacy.aol.com/puntos-importante).

### Personal Information

We collect personal information when you make your information known, such as by registering, authenticating, making purchases, or interacting with AOL. If you do not make yourself known to AOL, your use of our content and services is generally anonymous.

### How we use your Information

Your AOL information is used to operate and improve our services, fulfill your requests and communicate with you, conduct research, and personalize the content and advertisements provided to you.

### Information Sharing

AOL may share your personal information in limited circumstances, including when we have your consent to do so or when sharing is necessary to protect AOL or comply with the law. Our agents and contractors may have access to your information, but only to perform services for AOL. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties.

### Internet Advertising

Our ability to provide free content and services depends on advertising. Some of our ads are displayed based on the page visited, but many of our ads are targeted to you based on your interests and other information we have about you. We want you to understand how internet advertising works and offer resources and choices. [Learn more](http://privacy.aol.com/advertising-and-privacy/).

### How to Opt-Out

You can [opt-out](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) of targeted advertising delivered by the AOL Advertising Network.

### How to Contact Us

**AOL Privacy**  
22000 AOL Way  
Dulles, VA 20166  
privacyquestions@aol.com
